[
    {
        "front": "ちち",
        "back": "父 \nFather",
        "chapter": "N5 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "おとうさん",
        "back": "お父さん \nFather",
        "chapter": "N5 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "はは",
        "back": "母 \nMother",
        "chapter": "N5 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "おかあさん",
        "back": "お母さん \nMother",
        "chapter": "N5 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "さき",
        "back": "先 \nFuture, ahead",
        "chapter": "N5 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "せんげつ",
        "back": "先月 \nLast month",
        "chapter": "N5 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "うまれる",
        "back": "生まれる \nTo be born",
        "chapter": "N5 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "せんせい",
        "back": "先生 \nTeacher",
        "chapter": "N5 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "がくせい",
        "back": "学生 \nStudents",
        "chapter": "N5 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "だいがく",
        "back": "大学 \nUniversity",
        "chapter": "N5 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "がっこう",
        "back": "学校 \nSchool",
        "chapter": "N5 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "ともだち",
        "back": "友だち \nFriend",
        "chapter": "N5 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほん",
        "back": "本 \nBook",
        "chapter": "N5 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "にほん/にっぽん",
        "back": "日本 \nJapan",
        "chapter": "N5 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "まいにち",
        "back": "毎日 \nEvery day",
        "chapter": "N5 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "まいつき",
        "back": "毎月 \nEvery month",
        "chapter": "N5 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "まいとし/まいねん",
        "back": "毎年 \nEvery year",
        "chapter": "N5 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "なに",
        "back": "何 \nWhat",
        "chapter": "N5 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "なんがつ",
        "back": "何月 \nWhat month",
        "chapter": "N5 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "なんにん",
        "back": "何人 \nHow many people",
        "chapter": "N5 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "なんじ",
        "back": "何時 \nWhat time",
        "chapter": "N5 K5"
    }
]